<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Khoshrozeh</title>
    <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Khoshrozeh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 08:48:20 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TechTrove</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/projects/tech-blog-aggregator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:07:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/projects/tech-blog-aggregator/</guid>
      <description>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/tech-blog-aggregator/
Introduction TechTrove (placeholder name) is an aggregation site that provides references to useful engineering articles written by top tech companies. It allows for users to by topics and/or keywords (not implemented).
Inspiration The big O&amp;rsquo;Reilly books are great for general principles and developing your theoretical understanding but it always feel just a little detached. And it&amp;rsquo;s hard to find real production level examples of solutions on Youtube. Which is my I like the engineering blogs of the top tech companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS ETL Youtube Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/projects/aws-etl-youtube-pipeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 09:02:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/projects/aws-etl-youtube-pipeline/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack ➔ Languages: SQL, Python ➔ AWS Services: S3, Glue, QuickSight, Lambda, Athena, IAM ➔ SDK: AWS Data Wrangler
Introduction In this project, we&amp;rsquo;re simulating a client&amp;rsquo;s needs for a data-driven campaign through an AWS data pipline. Such a task could be useful for a client who plans to advertise on Youtube and wants to get better insight on what factors can help make a video more popular. SEE LEARNING GOALS Questions to answer:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Server Herd Architecture</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/projects/server-herd-architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 17:23:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/projects/server-herd-architecture/</guid>
      <description>Context This is a project I did from UCLA where I implemented a server herd architecture in Python. The idea for the architecture comes from the application server being a bottleneck. In the server herd architecture, multiple application servers communicate directly with each other and the core database, handling rapidly evolving data while the database manages more stable, less frequently accessed information. This project also explores using the asyncio library for communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drone Paths</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/projects/drone-paths/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 08:51:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/projects/drone-paths/</guid>
      <description>This was a really interesting project I did for my Graph Theory class at UCLA. The context for the problem is the following:
A company plans to use drones to drop sensors to the locations your scheme designated on the map, and wants your help on planning the routes of the drones. You are asked to work out two scenarios:
Scenario 1:
The company will use a large drone that can carry all the sensors; however, this drone consumes fuel fast, and thus it is important to minimize the total travel distance of the drone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
