<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Khoshrozeh</title>
    <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Khoshrozeh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:12:55 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Server Herd Architecture</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/projects/server-herd-architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 17:23:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/projects/server-herd-architecture/</guid>
      <description>Context This is a project I did from UCLA where I implemented a server herd architecture in Python. The idea for the architecture comes from the application server being a bottleneck. In the server herd architecture, multiple application servers communicate directly with each other and the core database, handling rapidly evolving data while the database manages more stable, less frequently accessed information. This project also explores using the asyncio library for communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drone Paths</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/projects/drone-paths/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 08:51:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/projects/drone-paths/</guid>
      <description>This was a really interesting project I did for my Graph Theory class at UCLA. The context for the problem is the following:
A company plans to use drones to drop sensors to the locations your scheme designated on the map, and wants your help on planning the routes of the drones. You are asked to work out two scenarios:
Scenario 1:
The company will use a large drone that can carry all the sensors; however, this drone consumes fuel fast, and thus it is important to minimize the total travel distance of the drone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Device Hardening</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/network-device-hardening/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:11:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/network-device-hardening/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this post, I&amp;rsquo;m going to go over some common threats and hardening techniques for various network devices including VPNs, routers, switches and more. Since organizations&amp;rsquo; networks are almost always a critical aspect of their security, it is important that the proper steps are taken to secure it. While no system can ever be 100% secure, we still can greatly reduce the organization&amp;rsquo;s risk by preventing, detecting and responding appropriately and promptly to attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTF Writeup: Lian Yu</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/lian-yu-writeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:48:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/lian-yu-writeup/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This CTF looks pretty straightforward based on the questions. I think I&amp;rsquo;ll try and do a speed run on it and do the writeup at the same time.
These are the questions:
What is the Web Directory you found? what is the file name you found? what is the FTP Password? what is the file name with SSH password? user.txt root.txt Let&amp;rsquo;s go!
CTF Directory enumeration: gobuster dir -u http://10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stabilizing Shells</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/stabilizing-shell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 16:00:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/stabilizing-shell/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Spawning shells in CTFs and pentesting is an extremely common task and we don&amp;rsquo;t want to have to deal getting disconnected from target, as well as the inconvenience of using a shell with limited shortcuts and controls. Here are 3 methods to stabilize your shell. Personally, I like to use Technique 1 in CTFs.
Technique 1: Python Applicable to on Linux, since they almost always have Python installed.
python -c &#39;import pty;pty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTF Writeup: Break Out the Cage</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/break-out-the-cage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 21:52:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/break-out-the-cage/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This CTF on TryHackMe has no instructions and only three questions:
What is Weston&amp;rsquo;s password? What&amp;rsquo;s the user flag? What&amp;rsquo;s the root flag? Let&amp;rsquo;s spin up the virtual machine and get hacking.
Break Out the Cage The only clue we start with is there&amp;rsquo;s a person named Weston.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with a TCP SYN port scan to see services are running, as well as gathering the service and OS information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recon Tactics and Tools with TomNomNom</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/tomnomnom-recon-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 13:51:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/tomnomnom-recon-tools/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this post I&amp;rsquo;m going to go over some reconnaissance tools, most of them built by well known and respected hacker TomNomNom, or Tom Hudson. I&amp;rsquo;m also going to cover some of his methodologies and techinques, for example how he utilizes VIM in his recon.
You can find and install his tools from his github.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to demonstrate some of these tactics on Admiral Labs which currently has a bug bounty on HackerOne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact/Links</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 11:32:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>akhoshrozeh@gmail.com
LinkedIn
Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTF Writeup: OWASP Juice Shop</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/owasp-juice-shop-writeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 01:58:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/owasp-juice-shop-writeup/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This CTF is called &amp;ldquo;OWASP Juice Shop&amp;rdquo; and is on the TryHackMe platform. It focuses on the following security concerns from the OWASP Top 10: Injection, Broken Authentication, Sensitive Data Exposure, Broken Access Control and Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). Let&amp;rsquo;s get started.
Task 1 This is simply spinning up the virtual machine and connecting to it through TryHackMe&amp;rsquo;s VPN. It is recommended to be familiar with Burp.
Task 2 We do some basic reconnaissance: just walking the applicaion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTF Writeup: RootMe</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/rootme-writeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 14:04:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/rootme-writeup/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here, I&amp;rsquo;m going to show how I solved the RootMe CTF on TryHackMe. It&amp;rsquo;s supposed to be for beginners so let&amp;rsquo;s jump in and find out!
Reconnaissance We’ll start with nmap to run a TCP SYN scan with some parallelism and collect service version information as well:
sudo nmap -sS -sV --min-parallelism 20 10.10.48.220
Note: we need to run SYN scans with escalated privileges because it is a more stealthy scan than say a TCP Connect scan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 11:48:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhoshrozeh.github.io/khoshrozeh.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I was born and raised in Los Angeles, CA. I graduated from UCLA with a B.S. in Computer Science in 2022. I am very passionate about all things related to cybersecurity, in particular penetration testing and hardening systems&amp;rsquo; security (networks, OS, software). I love learning new things and challenging myself through CTFs.
I am currently looking for work in the cybersecurity industry as an entry level penetration tester or security engineer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
